When two people meet,
and there's a spark,
they start testing the waters.
They want to know
how the other feels,
without giving
themselves away
too soon.
Everyone
keeps their feelings hidden.
But if they're brave enough,
they'll show the truth
to the one they love.
True love
brings two people
closer together.
Everyone loves differently.
Some act like
they don't care,
when really,
they care the most.
Love like that
is easy to miss.
But...
the right person
will always see it.
Then there are those
who never say
how they feel.
They keep it all inside
and never ask
how the other feels.
Hello?
You with me?
Lisa approved
our bracelet idea.
We're good to go!
Oh.
Go grab some lunch.
We'll go over
the details after.
Let's go.
Why didn't you say anything?
If I do now,
is it too late?
Hey!
Bad day?
What's it to you?
What are you doing?
I'm filming this.
Your meltdown
went viral last time.
Sorry. I was kidding.
(Elevator doors closing)
You show everything.
In this business,
that'll get you hurt.
So?
Hey,
we're supposed
to be a couple.
You can't even fake it.
How'll you
sell the romance?
I'll act when it's time.
I saw your viral video.
And I knew
you'd never dated.
You sure about that?
(Elevator doors closing)
Want a screen test?
Good enough?